The Abandoned Lullaby.
In the Dead
of Night, the
old record player
in the abandoned
nursery world to
life, casting an
eerie glow.
The warped vinyl
groans echoed through
the dusty halls,
playing a haunting
melody.
Children's laughter and
whispers replied, coming
from nowhere and
everywhere at once.
As the song
reached its crescendo,
the shadows coalesced
into human silhouettes,
dancing in the
static.
The player screeched
to silence.
A small door
creaked open, revealing
a miniature city
of toys, where
a hidden listener
awaited.
The record looped
back to the
start, beckoning another
eager ear to
join the children's
deadly game.
Will you answer
the call?