The cursed tapes,
in the depths
of the abandoned
asylum, a chilling
mystery awaited. A
dusty box, hidden
in the shadows,
contained a collection
of eerie recordings.
Each tape told
a tale of
despair, as patients
screamed in terror,
begging to be
silenced. But the
final tape was
different. It began
with a faint
whisper. Get out
while you still
can. The camera
shuddered, capturing the
face of the
sinister figure, illuminating
in the darkness.
His eyes glowed
with an otherworldly
light, as he
spoke
in a voice
that froze the
blood, I'm already
in. You're just
scratching the surface.
The screen flickered,
then went black.
The words, the
end, appeared, but
was quickly replaced
with a singular
message.
Continue listening.