The Dollmaker's Revenge.
In the decaying
town of Ravenswood,
a legend whispers
of the Dollmaker,
a madman who
created life-like figurines
to replace his
dead family. Years
later, the townsfolk
would hear faint
whispers and giggles
echoing from the
abandoned workshop. One
stormy night, a
group of friends
dared to
investigate. As they
crept inside, they
stumbled upon an
eerie exhibit. Dolls
with identical faces,
each adorned with
a faint smile.
Suddenly, the lights
flickered, and the
lights flickered, and
the doll's eyes
glowed. The friends
tried to run,
but the dolls
formed a circle,
trapping them.
The whispers ceased
as the dollmaker
reawakened. His creations
come to claim
his new family.