The cell phone
charger, I stumbled
upon an old
abandoned apartment complex
while exploring the
woods.
As I ventured
in, I noticed
an eerie glow
emanating from the
basement.
Curiosity got the
better of me,
and I descended
into darkness.
Rusty pipes scratched
beneath my feet,
accompanied by menacing
whispers on the
wind.
Suddenly, a sickly
bright light flickered,
revealing a single,
ancient cell phone
charger
atop a ratty
mattress. A single
cord, severed and
twisted by unknown
hands,
ended beside an
antique rotary phone.
Gripping the receiver,
I heard the
soft whisper,
Hello, hello, I
slammed the phone
down, witnessing its
twisted chord begin
to twitch,
plugging itself back
into the charger.
When I exited,
my footage showed
only static, and
the caption,
Ring. Ring.