The echo of
Blackwater Creek, overrun
with Ivy, the
old bridge creaked
in the dying
light of day.
Local legend whispered
that anyone who
ventured across would
hear the whispers
of Blackwater Creek's
victims.
Rachel had always
been skeptical, but
as she stepped
onto the rickety
boards, the wind
died, and the
only sound was
a faint singing.
It began with
a single phrase,
don't come back.
Then, a name,
Elizabeth. The words
grew closer, sweeter,
and more menacing.
until one phrase
cut through the
fog. You're coming
next. Rachel turned
back, but the
creek's darkness had
already consumed the
bridge, waiting for
its next unwary
visitor.