The last snowfall,
as the last
snowfall of the
season blanketed the
frozen town, a
sense of unease
crept over its
residence.
Among them was
an elderly woman,
Emily, who refused
to leave her
weathered cabin.
The wind howled
like a mournful
sigh outside, as
if aware of
the tragic event
about to unfold.
Suddenly, a faint
scratching sounded from
the wall, growing
louder with each
passing moment.
Emily's eyes froze
on the knotted
wood as the
scratching ceased.
Then, the door
creaked open, and
she saw the
snowy,
gaze of a
long forgotten face
etched on the
surface, a reminder
that in this
fleeting town, no
one truly stayed
buried.